Y-Y-Your Majesty!
I-I thought you were bedridden!
Mia, your sister's medicine
is truly incredible.
Thank you, sire.
Y-You've got it all wrong!
I have a report.
We found a poison at the Adenauer residence
identical to the one used here.
It was apparently furnished by Marquis Pyrz.
Pyrz. Have you anything
to say in your defense?
N-No, sire.
Very well.
Arrest Marquis and Marquise Adenauer,
as well as Marquis Pyrz
and anyone else involved
in this plot at once!
That goes for all who neglected
their duties in my absence.
I've already received accounts, documents,
and testimony proving all your wrongdoing,
including the attempt on my life!
Do you understand what this means, Pyrz?
You...
Your own son pleaded with me to stop you.
As for you, Julius...
F-Father!
I've seen all of your irredeemable behavior,
including your attempt on your brother's life.
F-Father!
Take him away.
Yes, sire!
Hey! Stop! Unhand me!
And so Julius's havoc comes to an end.
The groundwork to face the monsters
under the king's leadership is finally laid.
The battle for Girtonia's very existence
is about to begin.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
Episode 10
"What I Wish to Protect"
Himari reports that our knights
have been allowed entry into Girtonia.
I'm sure they're fighting monsters by now.
Granted, this delay was a huge setback.
I hope they made it in time.
Philia.
You should prepare yourself.
Brother, what do you—
Saint Philia!
I have returned!
Grace. Welcome back.
Your idea worked, Saint Philia.
I've made it so you can use this gem
to gather mana from me and my three sisters.
Thank you.
The ancient ritual known
as the magic-conversion spell
concentrates the magical power
of several people within a magistone
and imbues that magic into whoever wears it,
artificially allowing them
to bring massive power to bear.
Grace, I can't thank you
enough for what you've done.
No need to thank me at all!
Now, Saint Philia, bring our magic together!
Yes, let us begin.
I'm expanding the Great Purification
Circle over the continent.
This is it!
Show me what you can do, Philia Adenauer!
This is...
The mana is shining?
This is way brighter than last time!
With the magic power of five people
stretched to its limit, this time...
Here I go!
Saint Philia! This is incredible!
It's really expanding!
I-Is it?
Its purifying power is reaching
toward Bolmern!
I'm sure of it!
Saint Philia! Congratulations!
Is Girtonia saved now, too?
No, I'm afraid...
You failed, eh?
What do you mean?
The circle only covered
the western half of the continent.
The magic didn't convey properly
in Girtonia's direction.
You mean...
Our magic power wasn't enough?
No, it was more than enough.
But the mana to the east is far more
disrupted than I anticipated.
It prevented the circle's expansion.
I've failed.
What do I do?
This was supposed to be
the best way to help them...
I want to save Mia, and yet...
Every second counts, and yet...
The only way now... I'd have to put up
a pillar of light in Girtonia myself...
But...
If you leave the capital,
the Great Purification Circle
breaks down, right?
That's awful! Isn't there another way?
Grace!
Y-Yes?
Our magical power is linked now.
If you take over at the core for a while,
I would be able to go off on my own...
But that wouldn't be appropriate
for Parnacorta's saint.
Saint Philia!
You have to go!
Let me handle things here!
Yeah, if you can go,
there's no reason not to!
Grace... Prince Osvalt...
No, I cannot allow you to leave.
Brother...
I know you're smart enough to understand why.
I cannot let Parnacorta's saint
intervene in another kingdom's crisis
and endanger herself in the process.
And given the failure of the Great
Purification Circle's expansion,
I'll have to withdraw our knights
when the time comes as well.
But Brother—
I sympathize with the
Kingdom of Girtonia's plight,
and I recognize that Philia
feels obligated to her sister.
But even if this means you resent me,
I must act in the interests of my kingdom
and prioritize the safety
and future of our people.
Therefore, I must order
you to abandon the idea.
I agree with the prince.
C'mon, Big Sis!
Even if you tried to go now,
it would be too late.
Girtonia will be smothered
beneath the Demon Realm's power.
The rebirth of Archdemon Asmodeus
is all but inevitable.
We can't simply let you charge
into such a situation.
Good ol' Asmodeus is after the soul
of the legendary saint inside you, after all.
Miss Greatest...
Rather, Philia Adenauer.
If we lose you, the Great
Purification Circle will shatter.
The whole world will fall instantly
under the Demon Realm's control.
I was aware of that.
The course of action I suggested would mean
abandoning my post as the saint of Parnacorta.
But... But if I don't do it, Mia's going to...
Miss Philia!
Prince Osvalt?
Don't shoulder this burden alone.
Take a look around you.
Remember me saying that?
There's what my father told you, too.
I recommend that you become more selfish.
What is it you want to do?
What's right or wrong
isn't important right now.
Search deep inside you
and tell me what you really want!
I know exactly what I want.
I want to save Mia.
I just... want to save my sister!
Mia...
I want to save Mia!
I don't care what happens to me!
I want to save my sister!
You got it!
I'll get you where you need to go!
Wait a minute! Do you realize
what you're about to do?!
You'll be riding to your deaths!
Brother...
I'm supposed to lose
my own brother this time?!
Of course not!
I'm going so you don't have to lose anyone!
We don't have much time.
Miss Philia?
Right!
Grace, please—
I have it all handled!
Brother!
Highness!
We will return!
Think we should stop 'em?
They seem pretty determined.
I'm not sure we could.
Their chances are close to zero,
but we'll just have to hope
they save Girtonia.
Miss Philia, hold on tight.
I will.
Onward...
to Girtonia!
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
I won't let you lay a hand on Miss Mia!
I'm doing nothing more than
buying us time, but...
Good. Next—
All forces, charge!
The Parnacortan knights are here!
My sister's doing.
She trusted me to turn things around
and sent this charge on my behalf!
All right! My next barrier will—
It's not possible.
I sense countless monsters coming
from the Dark Forest.
Mia! Don't go!
H-Hey...
Should we just run?
You idiot! There's nowhere to run!
Run? Run where?
To Parnacorta, where my sister is?
Yes... that's a nice thought, isn't it?
If it seems likely something will befall
her, take her with you and run.
Is this that moment?
What did she just...
Miss Mia!
I could abandon my sainthood,
abandon everything,
join my sister in the next kingdom over,
forget everything, and start over!
How wonderful that would be!
I'm sure she and all her new
friends would welcome me.
We'd have such a lovely time together.
Silver Judgment!
Follow the saint!
But all that happiness...
How could I stand it?
After all, the person...
least deserving of that...
is me!
Pierre.
If it comes to it, do whatever
it takes to stop Mia.
What do you mean?
She hates herself.
In despair over what her
dear sister was put through,
she's sworn vengeance
on everyone responsible.
Which means...
Saint Mia!
That includes herself.
I'm sorry, my sister.
She will use the fulfillment
of her saintly duties to punish herself.
This will be the day that I die!
If we ride up this way,
we'll come to a plateau.
I'll create a pillar there and expand
the Great Purification Circle.
Understood.
Mia, let me be in time!
Silver Judgment!
I'm out of magic.
A saint without magic is just a burden.
But if I'm out, I can just make more.
I'll burn my life's energy
and convert it to magic.
It's a forbidden technique.
But if it will let me protect
as many people as possible...
I don't mind.
Judgment Arrow!
Begone! Begone! Begone!
Begone, begone, begone, begone, begone!
Begone!
S-Saint Mia...
This won't do.
Nothing good will come of losing her now!
Protect Saint Mia!
Protect the Kingdom of Girtonia!
I'm so glad... I was able
to act as a saint one last time...
Ah...
Is it over now?
It's dark. I'm so cold.
And I feel so sleepy.
I did work really hard.
I suppose I've earned some rest now.
Mia.
Someone's calling me?
Mia!
Oh... it's my sister!
She came for me!
We'll all be safe now.
Saint Mia! Saint Mia!
Silver Judgment!
Mia!
See? Just like I thought.
After all, my sister...
is my hero.
The monsters have been weakened!
Take this chance to slay them all!
Saint Philia!
Prince Osvalt!
Where are you?!
Miss Lena? Sir Leonardo?
Saint Heal!
How's it look?
I'll save her. I swear I will!
Her heartbeat is weakening.
Adjust her circulation...
Saint Heal!
Wake up, Mia!
Her wounds are healed.
Now it's up to her to stay strong.
I'm scared. I can't stop shaking.
What if she doesn't wake up?
Miss Philia.
Don't worry. I won't give up.
I will save you, Mia...
Because I'm your big sister!
Saint...
Heal!
S...
Mia?
S-Sister...
M-Mia...
Thank goodness you're safe.
So warm...
I thought I'd never see you again.
Because you're so determined
to fulfill your saintly duties,
I didn't think you'd come back.
You're right.
But I'm not acting as a saint right now.
I'm acting as your sister,
so I couldn't leave you behind.
Even if it wasn't the right decision,
I had to save you.
I...
When you left for Parnacorta,
I was so sad, so lonely,
I thought I might go crazy.
But more than anything, I was angry...
at everyone who took you for granted.
I wanted to take revenge on them.
Sister, I'm sorry I didn't see it all sooner.
Thank you for being angry on my behalf.
No one could have saved this kingdom but you.
You're a true saint now, Mia.
Philia...
Say, Big Sis.
Guess we were right not
to stop her from coming, huh?
She just got lucky. Honestly...
Prince Julius escaped?!
He can't have gone far! Find him!
D-D-Damn it!
I won't let this be the end!
If I can just get the power...
Is that it?
Just you wait, Mia...
I'll show you what happens
to those who betray me!
Now give me power!
Well done,
prince of Girtonia!
I never thought I'd be back here again.
Miss Philia, we managed to avoid
the worst-case scenario.
Yes, we did.
But only thanks to your aid, Prince Osvalt.
Not at all!
I didn't do anything.
You're the amazing one, Miss Philia.
Oh, hardly.
I never would have made it this far
without your encouragement.
I've never seen you this friendly
with a man before.
I never dreamed you'd find
a sweetheart over there!
Sweetheart?!
Mia, don't insinuate things like that.
You're bothering Prince Osvalt.
Well, I wouldn't call it a bother, exactly...
Too bad. I like him way better
than our louse of a prince.
But I'm just glad you seem happy!
Mia...
Your Majesty! Your Highness!
Hello, Philia, my destined one...
We meet again.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 11:
Next Time
Episode 11
"Archdemon Asmodeus"
"Archdemon Asmodeus."